자막제작:카블
Closet full of secrets and skeletons awakes but nothing's true
많은 비밀과 스켈레톤이 깨어났지만 진실도 없어
I used to own a castle now it's boxes that I have to move
난 성을 다스렸지만 이젠 내가 움직여야 할 짐일뿐이야
Right here in the darkness there's nothing left for me to do
여기 이 어둠에서 나에게 남은 할일은 없어
It's easier to run away but todayToday we got to
도망치는게 더 쉽지만 그러나 오늘은 기회가 왔어
Cast the shadows out from sight
어둠을 시야에서 떨쳐내려해도
A final stand a shouting cry
결국은 울음을 터뜨리네
All the wrongs now turned to right
잘못들은 이제 옳음으로 바뀌었어
So fight the past
그러니 과거에 맞서 싸워
Take back the night
밤을 되찾아
And call upon the torch tonight
오늘밤 많은 횃불이 필요해
To bring out all the ghosts to light
모든 유령들을 빛으로 쫓아내기 위해
Because at last we have to go it's time
우리는 결국 가야해 이젠 때가왔어
To take back the night
밤을 되찾아
Bridges burned and broken on different sides we start anew
다리가 다른 방향으로 부서지고 불탔어
우린 새로시작해야해
Being chased by monsters to face head on or be consumed
몬스터들에게 쫓기느냐 아니면 사로잡히냐
Reaching out for something grasping on to nothing to lose
움켜지는걸 찾아 아무것도 잃지 않기위해
Paybacks left too long unpaid but todayToday we got
너무 오랫동안 복수를 안했지만 이젠 기회가 왔어
to Cast the shadows out from sight
어둠을 눈앞에서 떨쳐내려해도
A final stand a shouting cry
결국은 울음을 터뜨리네
All the wrongs now turned to right
모든 잘못은 옳음으로 바뀌었어
So fight the past
과거에 맞서 싸워
Take back the night
밤을 되찾아
And call upon the torch tonight
오늘밤 토치가 필요해
To bring out all the ghosts to light
모든 유령들을 빛으로 쫓아내기 위해
Because at last we have to go
결국 우리는 가야해
it's time
바로 지금이야
To take back the night
밤을 되찾아
So fight the past
과거에 맞서 싸워
Take back the night
밤을 되찾아
To take back the night
And call upon the torch tonight
오늘밤 토치가 필요해
To bring out all the ghosts to light
모든 유령들을 빛으로 쫓아내기 위해
Because at last we have to go
결국 우리는 가야해
it's time
바로 지금이야
To take back the night
밤을 되찾아